OLEG SHEPELEV

+7-777-376-66-62

olegashepelev@gmail.com | linkedin

TECHNICAL SUMMARY

Languages: HTML/CSS/SASS/JavaScript

Frameworks: React JS, Express.js, Node JS, MongoDB

Networking: TCP/IP, HTTP(S)

Database: MySQL **IDE**: WebStorm

Issue & Project Tracking Software: Jira

ABOUT ME

I've been developing for about 6 years.

Basic knowledge of MongoDB, Mongoose, Express.js, Node.js, AJAX.

Skills in using HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, SASS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, React, Redux, Git,

Bootstrap, AntDesign, Figma, jira.

Adaptive layout skills according to BEM methodology.

Knowledge of English level B2.

EXPERIENCE

2022 JANUARY-JUNE

WEB DEVELOPER, TECHHOLDING

REMOTE

- Contract job until June
- Used technologies: React, Redux, TypeScript, Bootstrap, SCSS, AJAX, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

2021-PRESENT

WEB DEVELOPER, PROJECT WORK

REMOTE

- www.glampings.kz current project.
- Used technologies: React, Redux, TypeScript, antDesign, SCSS, AJAX, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

2016 MARCH-2021 MAY

WEB DEVELOPER, ATTRACTOR SCHOOL

REMOTELY IN THE FRAMEWORK OF TRAINING IN THE COURSES

- HTML/CSS/SCSS/BEM adaptive mobile layout, using Flex-box/Grid
- JavaScript > ES6/TypeScript
- iQuery
- React/Redux
- GIT

- AJAX
- Bootstrap/antDesign/Material-UI/UI Design

2006-PRESENT

PURCHASING MANAGER,

LLP MELOMAN-HOME-VIDEO

KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY

- In this company I started working as a sales consultant in a retail chain of stores.
- Purchase of products to the Microsoft Dynamics Axapta database.
- Training of junior employees in procurement.
- Control over the correct filling of all data for the purchase.
- Correction of miss-grading writing of defective goods and shortages.
- Adding new items to the database.
- Entering new overheads into the database.
- Advised accounting departments and capitalists department.
- I taught the employees of the accounting department to enter new names into the database, correctly create and distribute purchases, write off defective goods and shortages, and make returns based on purchases.
- Established the process of purchasing goods before they arrive at the warehouse.
- Implemented a business process for automating the procurement department.

2004-2006

PC OPERATOR, LLP CENTRAL HOUSE OF ACCOUNTANTS

KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY

- Typing, printing, copying on a copier.
- Sale of computer components and accessories.
- Installation of software at the request of customers.
- Delivery of office supplies.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2021 - 2022

WEB DEVELOPER, BOOTCAMP UDEMY COURSE THE COMPLETE 2022 WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

REMOTELY - INSTRUCTOR DR. ANGELA YU

2016 MARCH - 2017 MAY

WEB DEVELOPER, ATTRACTOR SCHOOL

REMOTE

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY,

KAZAKHSTAN INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES AND MANAGEMENT

KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY

COMPUTER DEVICE MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN,

PROFESSIOANL LYCEUM Nº1

KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY